nextcity.org 2014-11-30

# Privacy Policy – Next City

This Privacy Statement is applicable only to www.nextcity.org (the “Site”) and does not apply to any personal information that we may collect through other means, such as through other sites or offline.

### The Information We Gather About You & What We Do With It

Next City collects personal information that you voluntarily provide to us through the Site under the following circumstances:

  * If you request a subscription or purchase a product, we collect your name, email address and payment information. All credit card and billing address information used to purchase stories or subscriptions is gathered by and stored by Stripe.com. Next City never views your credit card information but may use your billing address information to deduce the regional demographics of our readership.
  * If you post a comment to our Site, we store your email address, username and any personal information provided in your comment.
  * If you opt in to our weekly e-newsletter, we collect your email address to provide you with Next City’s online content and events.
  * If you choose to log in to americancity.org through Facebook, Facebook sends us information from your Facebook profile. Do not log in to our Site through Facebook unless you agree that we may collect, store, and use any and all information made available to us through Facebook.

You may choose not to provide this personal information to us, but then we may not be able to provide you with services or products available on the Site.

### Cookies Policy

To enhance your experience on our Site, many of our webpages use “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering on nextcity.org. Once you choose to provide a webpage with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. A cookie is like an identification card. It is unique to your computer and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.

Cookies save you time as they help us to remember who you are. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products and services. We also use cookies to obtain analytical information related to user pageviews on our website, but this data does not contain personally identifiable information.

If you want to control which cookies you accept, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered by a website’s server. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser. You may find that some parts of the site will not function properly if you have refused cookies.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered by a website’s server. Please be aware that if you do not configure your browser you will accept cookies provided by this website.

### Information We Share and Transfer

Next City retains subscriber emails and names, which may be used for Next City’s marketing purposes and is occasionally made available to carefully screened companies whose products or services may be of interest to our readers. If you would like to be removed from this list, please write to info@nextcity.org with the subject heading “Marketing List Removal.”

In rare instances, we may disclose information about you to a third party if we are required to do so by law or feel that such action is necessary to prevent the misuse of our website, or the personal or public safety of our users or the public.

In the event that Next City changes leadership or sells or transfer all or a part of its assets, we reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you.

### How We Protect Information

We take reasonable physical, administrative and technical measures to protect your personal information. That being said, no measures are 100 percent secure; as a result we cannot guarantee the security of our Site or the personal information that you provide to us.

### Links to Other Sites

Our website contains links to other sites. If you use any of the links available on our Site, be aware that this Privacy Statement does not apply to the information collected on other sites. The privacy practices and statements pr policies of the other sites that you have accessed will apply. We are not responsible for the practices of any other sites that you may access through a link from our Site.

### For International Users

This site is governed by U.S. law. By using the Site, international users agree that the Site and their use of the Site is subject to U.S. law. International users who do not consent to the application of U.S. laws should not use the Site. This site is not intended for children under 13.

### For California Users: Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, we will refrain from sharing your personal information with third parties for their marketing purposes if you send us a request by email to info@americancity.org. All requests must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on the email subject line. For all requests, please clearly state that the request is related to “Your California Privacy Rights,” include your name and either your physical address (street address, city, state and zip code) or your email address. We will not accept requests via the telephone or by fax. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

### How to Contact Us

If you would like to update your personal information related to your account on nextcity.org, please visit the “My Account” section and edit your profile. Please email info@nextcity.org if you have questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement.
